On the rise of yours welcome all of you
to this video we start this video here first of all
if we see this Tamil
last Friday here we
got to see a report Delhi after this we can see crude oil at a
record high above 6300 and gold comfortably at
10 feet because of this
you can record your here because
do vest and subscribe to the channel
only and subscribe to doctor and book profit
after this if we look at the overall market
here Freddie's rise
phase can be seen from future but here in this
if you put Shravan of Sanjay Dutt
and do it because of this it can be done
after this if we talk about some branding
upside digit here the first
digit is information naukri.com's
revenue we see decreased by 22% here as compared to last year
they
can increase their profit this time by 600 that last
year or training so in a product launch
this comment as a guest who was here  But
due to the company selling its associate and joint venture assets, Bigg Boss made a
profit last year because
I can give you
a sea from the side of the fire shot S.
If we look at it here, it will increase the net profit by eight
percent and vitamins and nutrients will improve
that by 22% revenue. But if you look at
any of this, you can see below
but this course
gets Rs 532 financing,
you can see the big tomato here. So
now in this, we will take
its total collection of
speculative tests of 0.5 inches here and we will do this and the
chances of a fall here are quite
high. If you like this video, you can like our
channel link in the description and
comment below and if you like this video, then do not forget to
like it and subscribe to our channel. And if you like this video in the description box below, then
subscribe to our channel. If you like the
channel fish in the comment below
and you will say that
after this, if we talk about some planning stocks
here, then the first
stock is Happiness in Fact, in which
PM's sugar PM is here.
Subscribe to the National Highway Authority of India
construction
project in Uttar Pradesh.
Due to the reduction in subsidy on gas,
its name is Network. No
like this.
Go home and take your deposit in this company and you can
see the plan to increase it by 12.5% ​​here.
When the company is
going to set up its plant in Chittor district, due to this its power
cost will increase very quickly and this company
can move forward by removing itself from clean energy resources. Because of this, this
project has been seen in the last 85 years.
In the grocery stock of computers here,
whoever wants this deposit from one side will come here for the next few days.
Because of this, it has already worked on
its 1.5 million dollar solar
power project here. Due to this, this
quarter cannot be completed in the first quarter of 2022.
If we
see that digit, then here on Sunday
here and here we have a record next, so
you must watch the next video.  The scientist in